http://www.tescanada.com/privacy

EV Horn Driver DH2005
EV HF Diaphragm, (For DH3, DH2010A Driver)
EV, EVS-18S Recone Kit
EV,
DVX-3121 Recone Kit
EV,
EVX180B Recone Kit
EV,
EV ELX200 Full Range Amplifier/PSU PCB Assembly
EV,
ELX200 Subwoofer Amplifier/PSU PCB Assembly
EV,
ELX 200 Subwoofer Input PCB Assembly
EV,
ELX200-10 Input/Crossover Assembly
EV,
ELX200-12 Input/Crossover Assembly
EV,
EV Evolve 50 Sub Amplifier/PSU PCB Assembly
EV, Evolve 50 Subwoofer, 12"
A Brief Summary of Our Privacy Policy
Our Privacy Policy applies to your use of the TESCanada.com website. We only access information which is absolutely necessary to the functioning of the Web site and we do not share or sell this information to any third parties. In short, our practices are among the best available on the Internet.
Last update: August 26, 2019
Who We Are
Taylor Electronic Services Inc.,  A Private Corporation (“TES”) offers consultation, design, sales, installation, and onsite service of professional audio, video, lighting, surveillance equipment, and information technology.
About Our Privacy Policy
When you access this Web site, information is created. Because we know your privacy is important, we’ve created this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use and protect that information.
What information does our web site automatically collect?
IP Address, user agent, and the referring URL. When you visit our Web site we automatically receive your IP address and information such as the user-agent of your Web browser. This information is provided to us and every other Web site that you visit on the Internet by your Web browser.
What information do we know about you?
We don’t request or require you to provide personal information to access our Web site. As noted above, we may receive your IP address and user agent automatically. If you optionally elect to fill out our Contact, Parts Request, Service Repair or other form, we will receive all of the information you provide, such as Name, Email, Phone Number, and Company Name.
What about cookies?
The TES Web site may place cookies on your browser in order to identify you when you return to our web site.
How do we use the information collected by our web site?
We use aggregate information to understand how many total users have visited our web site and the types of devices on which they are using it.
We use information you choose to provide in our Web forms to sell parts and/or services.
Do we sell any of the information collected by the TES web site?
No. We don’t sell or rent the information to any third parties.
What’s the difference between personal information and aggregate information?
Personal information is information that can be used to identify a particular individual, generally understood to be information such as your name, physical address, email address and phone number. Aggregate information is not considered personal information and can’t be used to identify you.
Do we collect email addresses?
We do not require you to submit your email address, or any other personal information, to us in order to use the TES web site. If you use the information provided on the TES Web site to contact us directly (e.g., email us at ) we will receive your contact information, but will only use it in order to respond to your inquiry. If you fill out a Web form on our web site we receive your email and may store that email and associated contact information for up to 12 months.
How to Contact Us
Taylor Electronic Services Inc.,  A Private Corporation, is located at the following address:
Post office mail:
Taylor Electronic Services, Inc.
2075–16th Ave. E.
P.O. Box 606
Owen Sound, Ontario
Canada, N4K 5R4
Head office and courier delivery
Taylor Electronic Services, Inc.
2075–16th Ave. E.
Owen Sound, Ontario
Canada, N4K 5N3
Changes to this Privacy Policy
We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time based on changes to applicable laws and regulations or other requirements applicable to us, changes in technology, or changes to our business. Any changes we make to the Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page, so you should review it periodically. If there are significant changes to our information practices, specifically how we process personal information, you will be provided with appropriate online notice. We will also post a notice on our home page if our Privacy Policy has changed.
Hours: 8 AM - 4:30 PM, M-F
We're here to make you sound good.
Quick Links
Request Service Repair
Parts Request
Privacy Policy
Postal Address
For post office mail only
Taylor Electronic Services, Inc.
2075–16th Ave. E.
P.O. Box 606
Owen Sound, Ontario
Canada, N4K 5R4
Street Address
Head office and courier delivery
Taylor Electronic Services, Inc.
2075–16th Ave. E.
Owen Sound, Ontario
Canada, N4K 5N3
©
2020
by Taylor Electronic Services. All rights reserved.
Serving Owen Sound, Meaford, Collingwood, Blue Mountains, Hanover, Wiarton, Walkerton, Saugeen Shores, Kincardine, Port Elgin, Southampton, Barrie, South Bruce, Midland, Kitchener, Waterloo, Grey, Bruce, Wellington, Simcoe and Dufferin Counties
×
